# Liam Jackson

414 Shiloh Street, Austin, TX 78613 I iamjackson@exampl e.com (512)333-3333

Skilled leader in the food service industry with over eight years of experience in restaurants, a SafeServe Food Service Management certification, and a history of improving profitability and customer satisfaction. Comfortable managing a staff of more than 30 at once,

## Key Skills

- Organized
- Menu planning
- Microsoft Office Suite
- ♦ Inventory management
- Payroll processing and review
- Conflict resolution
- Supervising 30+ staff at once
- Strong verbal and written communication skills

## **Professional Experience**

## General Manager of Food Service

Bucee's, Austin, TX j June 2018 - Present

- Oversee food prep methods, portions, and presentation of food to ensure the item is prepared and presented in an acceptable manner
- Interview, train, and monitor employees and operations to ensure customer's expectations are exceeded
- Manage budgets and payroll to improve overall profitability
- \* Ensure that employee compliance with health and food safety standards
- Develop schedules end assign duties for over 50 employees each week

#### Kitchen Manager

The Cheesecake Factory, Temple, TX / May 2015 - May 2018

- Supervised kitchen employees and organize food orders
- Recruited and trained new hires in food safety, health standards, other company norms and expectations
- Monitored inventory levels and performed weekly inventory assessments
- Brought down supply cost by 15% by negotiating with vendors
- Resolved 90% of face-to-face complaints and used social media to improve 50% of restaurant's negative online ratings using social media

#### Assistant Kitchen Manager

The Melting Pot, Oklahoma City, OK ] March 2014- May 2015

- Managed daily operations and 8 kitchen staff under the direction of the general manager
- Ensured kitchen sanitation according to health and safety guidelines
- Streamlined food prep procedures, which resulted in a 5% profitability increase
- Evaluated guest feedback and managed to resolve 70% of in-person complaints without supervisory intervention

#### Line Cook

Whiskey Cake, Oklahoma City, OK j June 2012 - April 2014

- · Named "Employee of the Month" twice as one of only 60 restaurant employees
- Dedicated 3 extra hours a week to training new workers in food prep, storage, safety, and sanitation
- Prepared simple dish components by chopping vegetables, cutting meat, and preparing sauces

## Education

Associate of Applied Business Degree in Hospitality Management with a concentration in Culinary Arts

Tri-County Tech, Bartlesville, OK, September 2010 - June 2012

## Certifications

◆ SafeServ Food Safety Manager Certification 2018